Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - AIS Dance Component Phase Two Calendar Final Report (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Instructions to Panelists, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Grant Application to Ford Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - AIS Phase Two Application for Sites, Announcement re: Phase Two (Box 62)
  - IS Phase Two Request for Applications, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - NEA Grant Application for Follow-Up Program (with Ford Foundation) (Box 62)
  - NEA: AIS/DC Phase Two r70-51-96 Grant Letter and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Calendar, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Mesa, AZ (Mesa Public Schools) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Mesa, Arizona, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Tucson, AZ (Tucson Unified School District) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Tucson, Arizona, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Glendale, CA (Glendale Unified School District) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Glendale, California, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Orange, CA (Orange Unified School District) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Orange, California, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Rio Linda, CA (Rio Linda Union School District) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Rio Linda, California, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Fort Myers, FL (District School Board of Lee County) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Ft. Myers, Florida, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Aiea, HI (Alvah A. Scott Elementary) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Aiea, Hawaii, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Kahului, HI (Lihikai School) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Kahului, Maui, Hawaii, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Decatur, Illinois, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Decatur, IL (Decatur School District #61) (Box 62)
  - Alexandria, LA (Rapides Parish School Board) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Alexandria, Louisiana, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Winthrop, ME (Winthrop Public Schools) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Winthrop, Maine, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Marblehead, MA (Glover School) (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Marblehead, Massachusetts, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Phase Two Marblehead, Massachusetts, 1977-1978 (Box 62)
  - Coordinators, Dec. 16th (Box 63)
  - New York, Scheduling (Box 63)
  - New York. Letters from New York Companies (Box 63)
  - Chicago, Dec. 19th (Box 63)
  - San Francisco, Dec. 20th (Box 63)
  - Forms (Box 63)
  - Litvin Hand-Out (Box 63)
  - Mitchell Hand-Out (Box 63)
  - 1975-1976 Dance Touring Program Conferences for Dance Companies, Dec. 1974-Jan. 1975 (Box 63)
  - DTP Meetings, Correspondence, Dec. 1974-Jan. 1975 (Box 63)
  - Dance Touring Program FY 1975-1976 (held 1974-1975) Meeting for Dance Companies, Forms and Invitation Letters (Box 63)
  - DTP Conference Evaluations, Sept. 30-Oct. 1, 1974 (Box 63)
  - DTP National Meeting, Sept. 29-Oct. 1, 1974 (Box 63)
  - DTP: NEA Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - DTP: SAA Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - Dance Touring Program State Administrators, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - Dance Touring Program General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - DTP Lisa Booth Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - DTP Evaluation (Box 63)
  - DTP Regional Orientation Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - DTP, 1974-1975 (Box 63)
  - New Companies Meeting, 1972 (Box 63)
  - New Companies Meeting, 1970 (Box 63)
  - CLR Near East Europe Tour, July-Aug., 1966 (Box 63)
  - CU/CP (Box 63)
  - Wilfrid C. Stiff (Box 63)
  - Goslar/Brecht Circus Scene (Box 63)
  - Lottie Goslar General (Box 63)
  - Lottie Goslar Reviews (Box 63)
  - Nala (Box 63)
  - Nala Najan Correspondence (Box 63)
  - Nala Najan Photos (Box 63)
  - Nala Najan Press (Box 63)
  - Nala Najan General (Box 63)
  - Derek Hudson (Box 63)
  - Broadway, Paul Taylor, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Broadway Reviews, 1967 (Box 63)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Broadway, 1967 (Box 63)
  - Denby Article (Box 63)
  - Paul Taylor Press, 1967 (Box 63)
  - Taylor Reviews, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Taylor Reviews, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Paul Taylor Accounting (Box 64)
  - Chilean Prize (Box 64)
  - unlabeled correspondence and printed materials (Box 64)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 64)
  - Press Release and Bio (Box 64)
  - Company Information and Publicity, 1971-1972 (Box 64)
  - CRTP Press Clips, Testimonials, Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 64)
  - Local Sponsors' Brochures, Flyers, etc. that include residencies CRTP, 1972-1973 (Box 64)
  - Masters of Memos to State Arts Councils, 1973-1974 (Box 64)
  - Promotional Material (Box 64)
  - Disbursement: NEA Funds for CRTP1972-1973 (Box 64)
  - Status Survey SAC Cash Requests/Payments CRTP, Feb. 22, 1973 (Box 64)
  - NEA Checks Payable Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 64)
  - Compilations of Evaluations for CRTP, 1972-1973 (Box 64)
  - CRTP Guidelines, 1971-1972 (Box 64)
  - CRTP Evaluation Record, 1971-1972 (Box 64)
  - Senehan FYI Compendium, 1975-1976 (Box 64)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Dance Touring Program, 1972-1973 (Box 64)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, 1970 (Box 64)
  - NEA DTP, 1974 (Box 64)
  - Trisha Brown Photographs (Box 64)
  - Weidman (Box 64)
  - Taylor, Paul Printed Materials (Box 64)
  - Tharp Photographs (Box 64)
  - Nagrin, Daniel Printed Materials (Box 64)
  - Monk, Meredith Printed Materials (Box 64)
  - Nikolais Photographs (Box 64)
  - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company Brochure (Box 64)
  - Paul Taylor Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 64)
  - Paul Taylor Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 64)
  - New Hampshire SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New Hampshire Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New Hampshire Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - New Jersey Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - New Mexico Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New Mexico SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New Mexico Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Temporary File NY SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New York Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - New York CRTP, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - New York Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - New York SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - North Carolina Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - North Carolina SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - North Carolina Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Oklahoma SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Oklahoma Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Oklahoma Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Oregon Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - North Dakota Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Ohio SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Ohio Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Ohio Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Pennsylvania Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Pennsylvania SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Pennsylvania Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Puerto Rico Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Puerto Rico Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Puerto Rico SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Rhode Island SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Rhode Island Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Rhode Island Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - South Carolina SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - South Carolina Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - South Carolina State Arts Council, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - South Carolina Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - South Dakota SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - South Dakota Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - South Dakota Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Texas SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Texas Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Texas Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Utah Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Utah SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Utah Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Vermont Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Virginia SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Virginia Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Virginia Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - U.S. Virgin Islands SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Washington DC Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Washington DC SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Washington DC Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Washington SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Washington Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Washington Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Wisconsin Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Wisconsin SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Wisconsin Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Wyoming SAC Grant Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Wyoming Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - Wyoming Evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
  - Evaluation Forms with Problems, 1972-1974 (Box 65)
  - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65)
  - CRTP Alabama (Box 65)
  - CRTP Alaska (Box 65)
  - CRTP Arizona (Box 65)
  - CRTP Arkansas (Box 65)
  - CRTP California (Box 65)
  - CRTP Colorado (Box 65)
  - CRTP Connecticut (Box 65)
  - CRTP Delaware (Box 65)
  - CRTP Florida (Box 65)
  - CRTP Georgia (Box 65)
  - CRTP Hawaii (Box 65)
  - CRTP Illinois (Box 65)
  - CRTP Indiana (Box 65)
  - CRTP Iowa (Box 65)
  - CRTP Kansas (Box 65)
  - CRTP Kentucky (Box 65)
  - CRTP Louisiana (Box 65)
  - CRTP Maine (Box 65)
  - CRTP Maryland (Box 65)
  - CRTP Massachusetts (Box 65)
  - CRTP Michigan (Box 65)
  - CRTP Minnesota (Box 65)
  - CRTP Missouri (Box 65)
  - CRTP Montana (Box 65)
  - CRTP Nebraska (Box 65)
  - CRTP Nevada (Box 65)
  - CRTP New Hampshire (Box 65)
  - CRTP New Jersey (Box 65)
  - CRTP New Mexico (Box 65)
  - CRTP New Mexico (Box 65)
  - CRTP New York (Box 66)
  - CRTP North Carolina (Box 66)
  - CRTP North Dakota (Box 66)
  - CRTP Ohio (Box 66)
  - CRTP Oklahoma (Box 66)
  - CRTP Oregon (Box 66)
  - CRTP Pennsylvania (Box 66)
  - CRTP Puerto Rico (Box 66)
  - CRTP Rhode Island (Box 66)
  - CRTP South Carolina (Box 66)
  - CRTP South Dakota (Box 66)
  - CRTP Tennessee (Box 66)
  - CRTP Texas (Box 66)
  - CRTP Utah (Box 66)
  - CRTP Vermont (Box 66)
  - CRTP Virginia (Box 66)
  - CRTP Virgin Islands (Box 66)
  - CRTP Washington DC (Box 66)
  - CRTP Washington State (Box 66)
  - CRTP West Virginia (Box 66)
  - CRTP Wisconsin (Box 66)
  - CRTP Wyoming (Box 66)
  - Future Projections CRTP, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - CRTP Guidelines, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - Company Forms, 1973-1973 (Box 66)
  - CRTP Company Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 1972 (Box 66)
  - CRTP State Arts Councils Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - CRTP Memos to Local Sponsors, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - CR Invitations to Speak, Meetings, etc. Follow Up (Box 66)
  - AADC Ad Hoc Committee and Other Misunderstandings of CRTP (Box 66)
  - Company Interim Reports CRTP FY 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - Evaluation Form Tally on Sponsor Return (Box 66)
  - "How to Organize a Local Sponsor" CR for Meetings (Box 66)
  - State Arts Councils Responses to Requests for Lists of Potential Local Sponsors, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - CRTP Master Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - CRTP State Lists (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines for Sponsors, 1975 (Box 66)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program for Dance Companies Guidelines, 1974 (Box 66)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program Directory of Dance Companies, 1974 (Box 66)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program Directory of Dance Companies, 1975 (Box 66)
  - Coordinated Residency Touring Program Forms, 1973-1974 (Box 66)
  - Dance Program Guidelines, 1974 (Box 66)
  - Dance Touring Program Directory of Dance Companies, 1976 (Box 66)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines for Sponsors, 1976 (Box 66)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines for State Arts Agencies, 1975 (Box 66)
  - Dance Touring Program Guidelines for Dance Companies, 1975 (Box 66)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company: Eileen Cropley Cartwright, 1960 (Box 66)
  - Pictures from Denmark, 1956-1961 (Box 66)
  - Pictures from Denmark, 1956-1961 (Box 66)
  - Alabama Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Alaska Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Arizona Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - California Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Colorado Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Connecticut Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Delaware Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Florida Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Georgia Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Hawaii Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Illinois Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Iowa Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Kentucky Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Louisiana Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Maine Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Maryland Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Minnesota Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Missouri Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - New Jersey Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - New Mexico Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - New York Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - North Carolina Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Ohio Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Oklahoma Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Pennsylvania Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Rhode Island Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - South Carolina Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Texas Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Virginia Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Virgin Islands Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Washington DC Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Washington Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - Wisconsin Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - AIS Budget Info General (Box 67)
  - AIS Workshop Total Expenses, 1979 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component DMS Requests for Assistants, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - AIS Workshop Expenses, Summer Workshop Planning Meeting, Mar. 18, 1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Workshop Expenses, Housing, 1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Workshop Expenses, Jazz Component, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop Jazz Component, 1980 (Box 67)
  - DMS Independent Contractor Status (Unemployment, etc.) (Box 67)
  - Independent Contractor Statements from DMS AIS Program, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop Planning Meeting Notes, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop L(*) Payment Exceptions Observers, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Workshop Registration (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop Site and Meal Meetings, 1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Equipment, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop Assorted Letters Accompanying Registration, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Summer Workshop Exception Paid Participant (Box 67)
  - Reminders for Schedules and Reports (Box 67)
  - Contact Sheet Original, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Memorandums (Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence with Artists (Box 67)
  - Memos: Delinquent Reports (Box 67)
  - Residency Report Memos (Box 67)
  - Payment Procedure, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Payment Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Payment Exceptions, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Dance Component Log Sheets, 1978-1979 (Box 67)
  - Log-In Books, 1975-1978 (Box 67)
  - AIS Artists Reports (Box 67)
  - Artists Reports Regional Dance Agencies, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - NEA Correspondence (Box 67)
  - AIS Itinerary, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Site Visits, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - Site Visits, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Ohio Trip (Box 67)
  - AIS Trip Report, 1979-1980 (Box 67)
  - AIS Trip Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Trip Visits, Reports Miscellaneous (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Litchfield, CT, Nov. 18, 1975 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Wilmington, DE, Dec. 11, 1975 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Missouri and Tennessee, Oct. 6-12, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit NYC PS 75, Dec. 9, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit N. Brunswick, NJ, Jan. 27, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visits, Feb. 3-12, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit NYC PS 98, Mar. 8, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visits, Mar. 22-25, 1976 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visits, Feb. 14-17, 1977 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Hartford, CT, Feb. 17, 1977 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Elizabethtown, PA, Mar. 10, 1977 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visits, Mar. 16-22, 1977 (Box 67)
  - AIS/Dance Component Site Visit Boston, MA, Apr. 6, 1977 (Box 67)
  - AIS Program Directory, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Artists-In-Schools Program/Dance Component Directory of Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Artists-In-Schools Program/Dance Component Directory of Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1980-1981 (Box 67)
  - Coordinated Touring Residency Program (Box 68)
  - LB-DTP Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Lisa Phone Conversation, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - LB Correspondence DTP, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Sponsor Company Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Specific Company Requests, California and Western States, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Company Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Requests, No Specific Company, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - NEA Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - State Arts Council Correspondence CRTP, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP West, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - State Arts Council Correspondence CRTP, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Requests, Specific Company, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Guidelines, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Company Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Company Reports, CRTP Booking Schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Contract Status Charts, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - State Work Sheets, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Waiting List, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Waiting List West, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Waiting List, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Waiting List, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Waiting List, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Calendar Changes, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Masters of Memos to Companies, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - CRTP Masters of Letters and Memoranda to Sponsors, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Work on Evaluation Form for Companies (Box 68)
  - CRTP Company Statement and IRS Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - Company IRS Letters, etc. (Box 68)
  - CRTP Make Payable Forms, Correspondence (Box 68)
  - CRTP Completed Return Forms from Participating Local Sponsors, 1973-1974 (Box 68)
  - State Arts Councils Address and Peeps (Box 68)
  - FY 1974 CRTP Directory Company Questionnaire (Box 68)
  - FY 1974 CRTP Directory Company Questionnaire (Box 68)
  - AIS/Dance Component Final Report, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Evaluations from Lydia Joel, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component California, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Alabama, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Oregon, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Pennsylvania, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Ohio, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Guidelines and General Information, 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component General Information, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS State Lists Re: Art Form Preferences for AIS, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - Impact AIS Dance Component, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Administrative Information, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component California, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Alabama, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Ohio, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Oregon, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Pennsylvania, 1971-1972 (Box 69)
  - AIS General Info, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS General, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS Puerto Rico, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component U.S. Office of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component General, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Movement Teacher General File, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Impact Report by K. Bloom, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Final Report, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS/Dance Component Calendars, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - AIS Guidelines, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - Alabama, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - Alaska, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - California, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 69)
  - Ririe-Woodbury Point System (Box 70)
  - AIS Tentative Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - Sponsor Development and Funding Source List (Box 70)
  - "About Education--The Arts--Basic" (Box 70)
  - Individual State Meetings A Checklist for Participants (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Apr. 1977 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Nov. 1976 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Sept. 1976 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., June 1976 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Feb. 1976 (Box 70)
  - AIS Letter of Agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Sept. 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., June 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., May 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Apr. 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Mar. 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Feb. 1978 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Dec. 1977 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., June 1977 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Fall, 1980 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., June 1980 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Spring, 1980 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Winter, 1980 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Fall, 1979 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., May 1979 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Apr. 1979 (Box 70)
  - F.Y.I., Dec. 1978 (Box 70)
  - AIS Workshop Registration Form, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - AIS Workshop Evaluation Form, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - Architects-in-Schools Booklet (Box 70)
  - Ted Taylor's Scheduling Form (Box 70)
  - Your Role in the AIE/DC (Box 70)
  - National Committee: Arts for the Handicapped (Box 70)
  - Presenting Performances: A Handbook for Sponsors (Box 70)
  - National Dance Association Brochure (Box 70)
  - Introduction to Dance Lighting (Box 70)
  - Books About Dancing (Box 70)
  - "Questions to Consider" (Box 70)
  - History of AIS (Box 70)
  - NEA Press Release for 1980-1981 Workshop (Box 70)
  - Your Role in the AIS/Dance Component Pre-1980 (Box 70)
  - Dance for the Handicapped Outline from "Anne's Magic" (Box 70)
  - AIS Calendar and Payment Schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Participants List, 1980 (Box 70)
  - "Brain's Division of Labor" (Box 70)
  - "Press Photography for Dance Companies" by Jack Mitchell (Box 70)
  - Job of State Coordinator, 1977-1978 (Box 70)
  - Dancing in the Schools Booklet (Box 70)
  - AAC (Box 70)
  - National Coordination Letters from Educators, 1978-1979 (Box 70)
  - Artists Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 70)
  - Meeting for National Coordinators NEA, Oct. 12, 1978 (Box 70)
  - AIS/Dance Component Grant 92-5111-077 Cash Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 70)
  - AIS/Dance Component NEA Grant 92-5111-077, 1979-1980 (Box 70)
  - AIS Workshop Exceptions for Attendance, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Room and Board Records AIS Workshop, 1978 (Box 70)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Expenses, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Fee Exceptions AIS Summer Workshop, 1979 (Box 70)
  - AADC National Meeting, June 1975 (Box 70)
  - Association of American Dance Companies (Box 70)
  - Association of American Dance Companies Sixth Annual Conference, June 1972 (Box 70)
  - ETS: Dance Panel Meeting (Box 70)
  - Arts Recognition and Talent Search Dance Semifinalists (Box 70)
  - Scholars in the Arts Dance Semifinalists (Box 70)
  - Arts Recognition and Talent Search, Jan. 4, 1983 (Box 70)
  - Scholars in the Arts Semifinalists in Dance (Box 70)
  - ARTS Dance Videotape Evaluations, Jan. 9, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Arts Recognition and Talent Search Report of Dance Panel Meeting, Oct. 22, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Arts Recognition and Talent Search, Jan. 31, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Dance Panel Meeting, Aug. 8-9, 1980 (Box 70)
  - ARTS Dance Panel, Oct. 17, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund, Feb. 1983 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1981-1982 Programs, Aug. 1982 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1980-1981 Programs, July 1981 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund, 1981 (Box 70)
  - TDF Board and Committee Meetings Minutes, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1979-1980 Programs, July 1980 (Box 70)
  - Theatre Development Fund Information on 1979-1980 Programs, July 1980 (Box 70)
  - TDF Board and Committee Meetings Info, 1980 (Box 71)
  - TDF Miscellaneous Information and Correspondence, 1980 (Box 71)
  - TDF Board and Committee Meetings Info, 1979 (Box 71)